Super Grass is a comedy film directed by Tom Vaughan.
Greg is growing a marijuana plant in his basement flat.
When his parents visit he gives them "herb" tea.
After becoming very giggly they leave.
After this Greg's friend arrives and they smoke a joint together.
Then his gran arrives with her friend who steals some of the plant.
Then the drug squad arrive.
Greg, played by Charlie Creed-Miles.
Dad, played by Nick Dunning.
Derek, played by Norman Roberts.
Mum, played by Sharon Duce.
Stoner film is a subgenre of comedy film based on marijuana themes, where recreational use often drives the
plot, sometimes representing cannabis culture more broadly or intended for that audience.
The tone is lighthearted.